国会让美国失望
全国教师罢工  集会抗议总统教育改革
罢工已持续近一个月
We're almost a month into the strike,
无数孩子待在家里不能上学
and we've got millions of kids stuck home from school.
你会不会责怪白宫或国会
Do you blame the White House or Congress?
我个人并不同情那些老师
I personally have very little sympathy for the teachers.
国会让教师失望
罢工已持续超过三周
We're over three weeks into this strike.
国家损失了几十亿美元
It's costing the country billions of dollars,
他们不提供解决方案  而是...
and instead of offering solutions--
表明立场和坐视不理
There's a big difference between
你们的工会榨干我们的税金
是两种截然不同的态度
taking a stand and sitting on your hands.
我不知道这叫不叫懦弱
I don't know whether to call it cowardice...
教师应该教书  回家吧
这是他的议程
It's his agenda,
问题在于他剽窃了合理的保守党思想
and the problem is that he stole sound, conservative ideas.
他唯一明智的决定
The only smart thing he's done
是抄袭了共和党的党章
is lift his platform from the republican platform.
我承认  琳达  我没料到会这样
I admit it, Linda. This got away from me.
但时间不能倒转  我们必须坚守阵地
But we can't turn back time. We have to hold our ground.
不管我们的支持率持续下滑吗
While our approval ratings continue to nosedive?
斯比奈拉和我多年来
Spinella and I worked together
合作完成了很多跟劳工相关的法案
for years on dozens of labor-related bills.
-我以为他会讲理  -你弄错了
- I thought he'd be reasonable. - You were wrong about that.
我没想到他会疯狂到发起罢工
Well, I didn't think he'd be insane enough to go on strike,
也没想到罢工会持续那么久
and I didn't think the strike would last this long.
那你就错了两次
So you've been wrong twice about this.
我为什么要相信你该坚守阵地
Why should I believe you're right about holding out?
我们为了绩效标准
We threatened collective bargaining
和特许学校拨款而要挟集体谈判
in order to get performance standards and charter funding.
这是我们的条件  我们的立场
That's the deal that we made. We took that stand.
我们现在妥协  就会一输到底
We lay down now, we lose it all.
法案将彻底失去改革性
There'll be no reform, just an empty bill.
这道理我明白  弗兰克
I understand the logic, Frank,
但我们现在要控制损失
but we're in damage control now.
我们不能拆东墙补西墙
We can't close one wound by opening another.
但我们是民主党
But we're the democrats.
我们理应维护教师
We're the ones who are supposed to be defending the teachers.
鱼和熊掌  琳达
But you can't have it both ways, Linda.
你不能既要改革
You can't have the reform you want
又想让教师满意
and keep the teachers happy at the same time.
这你一开始就知道
You knew that when we started.
好  如果我们要选择
Okay, then if we have to choose,
我们选择让教师满意
we choose to keep the teachers happy.
这样不对  琳达  我们已经没退路了
That is a mistake, Linda. We've already crossed the rubicon.
实话跟你说  总统想修改法案
I'm telling you this-- the president wants to change the bill.
三周前就该这么做  我们没有
We should've done it three weeks ago. We didn't.
所以现在你必须改
So you have to do it now.
再给我点时间  琳达  拜托
Give me more time, Linda, please.
如果我能结束罢工
If I can break this strike
并保留法案的全部条款
and get everything we want in this bill,
你能不能说这比认输更好
can we agree that's preferable to folding?
当然  如果这真能做到...
Of course. If we can count on that--
那就再信我一星期
Then count on me for just one more week.
如果到时罢工还没结束  我就改法案
If the strike isn't over by then, I'll change the bill.
-弗兰克  -不  一星期  仅此而已
- Frank-- - No. One more week. That's all.
这是最糟的处境
This is the worst possible position to be in.
如果我修改法案
If I water down the bill,
总统还是会认为我失败了
the president will still see me as a failure.
如果罢工一周内不结束
If the strike doesn't end in a week,
我等于把自己逼到墙角
I forced myself into a corner.
只有绝对的胜利才能让我重获他的青睐
Only total victory will put me back in his good graces.
否则就是出局
The alternative is exile,
那么过去五个月都白费了
which would mean the last five months were for nothing.
我绝不能跌回原地
I cannot abide falling back to square one.
议员找我吗  太太
Does congressman need me, ma'am?
不是  我只是想问你要不要来杯咖啡
No. I just was wondering if you wanted a cup of coffee.
我刚烧好一壶
I just brewed a fresh pot.
-不用了  太太  谢谢  -你确定
- I'm good, ma'am. But thanks. - Are you sure?
再过几小时就换班了  我没事
My shift's done in a couple hours. I'll be fine.
进来吧  放松一下
No. Come on. Stretch your legs.
别想拒绝我
I won't take no for an answer.
你做议员保镖前是干什么的
What did you do before you joined the leadership detail?
我是华盛顿的警察
I was a cop here in DC.
再之前  在海军陆战队  太太
Before that, I was in the Marines, ma'am.
-谢谢  -你在国外服过役吗
- Thank you. - Did you serve overseas?
是的  太太  巴林  还有阿富汗
I did, ma'am. Bahrain, then Afghanistan.
第二次驻派海外基本是在可兰山谷
Served most of my second tour in the Korangal Valley.
可兰山谷: 位于阿富汗  又称"死亡山谷"
您想问我有没有杀过人
You wanna know if I killed anyone?
我想我知道答案了
I think I know the answer.
我和博奇吃晚餐  我要
I got a dinner meeting with Birch. I'll be...
我请他进来喝杯咖啡
I invited him in for coffee.
快点喝  我们五分钟内就要走
Well, drink it fast. We leave in five...
趴下  别靠近窗口
Get down! Stay away from the windows!
站住
Stop!
我会派六名最好的手下24小时保护您
You'll have six of my best men covering you around the clock.
我好奇为什么现在保护我们的
I guess I'm wondering why we didn't at least have
没有一个是你最好的手下
one of your best men covering us now.
他会受处罚的  先生
He'll be disciplined, sir.
他在居民区开枪
He shot a gun in a residential neighborhood.
-炒了他  -我们会进行彻底调查
- I want him fired. - There will be a full investigation,
我们会采取必要的措施
and we'll take the necessary action.
要是史蒂夫在就没这种事了
Steve never would've let this happen.
他好点了吗
Is he better yet?
他在的话我会安心许多
Because I would feel a lot safer if he was with us.
很遗憾  他不会回来了  先生
Unfortunately, he won't be coming back, sir.
我以为他只是胆囊感染
I thought he just had a gallbladder infection.
是的  但还有更重的问题
He did, but they found more.
胰腺癌晚期
His pancreas, stage four.
-天哪  -真可怕
- Jesus. - Oh, my God. That's awful.
他还能活多久
How much longer does he have?
不多  只有几周
Not long. A few weeks.
至少他妻子是这么说的
At least that's what his wife told me.
我们得去看看他  你能打听他在哪吗
We have to go see him. Can you get the information where he is?
当然  我查到马上告诉您
Of course. I'll make sure you get it right away.
-谢谢你  队长  -谢谢
- Thank you, Captain. - Thank you.
不用谢  晚安
You're welcome. Good night.
-前门  -是
- Front door. - Yes, sir.
武器给我
Your weapon.
还有徽章
Your badge too.
我被停职了吗
Am I suspended, sir?
嫌犯徒步逃跑  你居然开枪
You had a suspect on foot, and you fire your gun?
长官  我知道
Sir, I realize that--
你知道这让我多丢人吗
Do you know how this reflects on me?
我的手下这么没有分寸
That one of our men could be so careless?
你不仅擅自离岗去喝咖啡
Not only do you abandon your post for coffee...
你要是射伤路人呢
You could've killed a bystander.
你的子弹打中别人前门
That slug was found in somebody's front stoop.
万一打进屋里了呢
What if it went in their house?
徽章  密查姆
Your badge, Meechum.
两个原因  其实都一样
Two reasons, which are really the same reason.
我受够给别人打工了
I was sick of working for other people,
而且我知道自己比老板更出色
and I knew I could do a better job than my bosses.
他们总想打压我  排斥我
They kept trying to suppress me, shutting me out.
我就想  我按自己的方式来吧
So I said, "Fuck it. I'll do it my way."
-然后你就辞职了  -和你不一样
- Then you just quit? - Not like you did.
我忍到攒够钱开头条网才走的
I slaved away until I lined up the money to start Slugline.
头条网做大以后你有什么计划
Once Slugline gets big enough, what's the plan?
像阿里安娜那样卖掉它吗
Are you gonna sell it like Arianna?
阿里安娜・赫芬顿: 《赫芬顿邮报》网站创始人
该网站于2011年被美国在线以3亿1千5百万美元收购
可能吧  然后谁知道呢
Probably. And then who knows?
迎接任何新挑战  说不定会去上海
Whatever the next adventure is. Maybe Shanghai.
那么我得准备好两年后重新找工作咯
So I shouldn't expect to have a job in two years?
你真会愿意同一份工作干两年吗
Do you ever wanna have any job for more than two years?
你又有什么计划
What about you? What's your big plan?
还没想好
Uh, I don't know yet.
得了吧  头条网只是你的垫脚石
Come on. Slugline is just a stepping stone for you.
-我得去接一下这个  -快去吧
- You know what? I should take this. - Go. Do your thing.
你能证明是斯比奈拉指使的吗
Hey. You have proof Spinella was behind it?
写下来  全国教师罢工的第三周
Put it in context. Three weeks into a national teachers' strike--
法案负责人弗兰西斯・安德伍德议员家中...
At the home of Francis Underwood, who has led the charge on--
这就对了  赶快发布
There you go. Now post that
免得我邻居先打给了11点地方新闻
before one of my neighbors calls a local 11:00 hack.
我什么时候可以见你
When do I see you next?
我是此事的受害者  不是联络人
I'm background on this. I'm not your source.
你现在不方便吗
You can't talk now?
-不  -那什么时候方便
- No. - When?
很快我就会乐意见你
Soon, with bells on.
"多些书籍少点砖头"怎么样
What about "More school books, less bricks"?
太宽泛了  这一口要咬得准一点
Nah, it's too broad. We need a better sound bite.
要具体点
Something specific,
能直接把矛头指向斯比奈拉
something that points the finger directly at Spinella.
-他会否认与之有关  -他当然会
- He'll deny any involvement. - Of course he will.
所以我们该怎么说
So how do we get around that?
我们说他管不住他手下
We say he can't control his troops.
-没有证据表明那是老师  -不然会是谁
- There's no evidence it was a teacher. - Who else could it be?
他会把罢工的起因推回国会身上
He's gonna shift blame for the strike back on congress.
不行  我们的论点要简单  无可辩驳
No. We need something clear, something clean,
让人能记住
something that sticks in your head.
教师需要学会自制
"Teachers need a lesson in self-restraint."
不  你没懂我说的  大家都爱戴老师
No. You're not hearing me. People like teachers.
我们要让斯比奈拉做那个恶人
No. We need something that makes Spinella the villain.
-他的不作为  无能  -无组织劳工
- His lack of control, his inability-- - Disorganized labor.
显而易见  这是无组织劳工
It's disorganized labor, plain and simple.
罢工教师转向暴力
当愤怒的教师
When you've got angry teachers
开始朝国会议员的窗户扔砖头
throwing bricks through congressmen's windows,
工会领袖必须受谴责
you've gotta blame the union leadership.
我们将为所有高层议员增加安保
We'll be beefing up the security for the entire leadership.
我强烈建议马蒂・斯比奈拉
And I strongly encourage Marty Spinella
管好他的人
to keep his people in line.
现在变得像无组织劳工了
This is starting to look like disorganized labor.
你真的认为马蒂・斯比奈拉该对此负责吗
Do you really think Marty Spinella is to blame?
无论斯比奈拉先生是不是主使
Whether Mr. Spinella is behind this or not,
他应该少花功夫打花枪
he might wanna tone down the rhetoric
以免无组织劳工发展成有组织犯罪
before disorganized labor turns into organized crime.
没人拿得出证据  这是最有力的回应
No one can prove anything. So that's the most cogent response.
那就上电视解释啊
Well, go on TV and say that.
你憎恶任何形式的暴力
You deplore violence in any form.
应当负责任的是国会
It's congress that should take responsibility.
我不想自贬到弗兰克的档次
I don't want to degenerate to Frank's level.
我们要解决砖头的事
We need to kill this brick thing.
否则人们的注意力都被转移了
It's distracting people from the issues.
-她说的对  -故事传一圈就没了
- She's right. - It'll eat up one cycle, and it'll disappear.
不  投砖事件越来越受瞩目
No. This story is getting traction.
罢工支持率正在下降
Support for the strike is dipping.
总统支持率不也是吗
So is the president's approval ratings.
不管怎样
But he gets to say in the
他还能继续执掌白宫三年
oval office another three years, no matter what.
我们可再拖不起三个星期了
We can't afford another three weeks.
我鼓动工会罢工时
When I told the unions to strike,
跟他们说了这会是持久战
I told them to prepare for the long haul, all right?
即使把他们拖穷了  我们也得继续
Their accounts dry up, we keep going.
我们会想出办法的
We figure it out.
这事我不能就这么不清不楚地认了
I am not going to blink over something like this.
话是这么说  但我们要是输了公关
Fine. But if we lose the public relations battle,
再坚持又有什么用
none of that does us any good.
弗兰克想迫使我们采取防守
Frank wants us on the defensive.
我认为投砖事件会平息的
I think this story is going to blow over.
要是我错了  我们再做定夺
If I'm wrong, we'll reevaluate.
但我想再坚持一两天  好吗
But I wanna give it another day or two first. Okay?
亚当
Hi, Adam.
你没事吧  我看了新闻
You all right? I saw the news.
我没事
Yes, I'm fine.
肯定让人很不安吧
That's gotta rattle the nerves--
砖头从窗户砸了进来
a brick coming through the window.
是有点
It did, some.
你现在还住在家里吗
So are you staying in the house?
已经加派了保安  所以...
We've got extra security now, so...
我挺担心的
Well, um, it made me think of you,
就想打电话问候一声
so I figured I'd just check in.
谢谢你了
I appreciate that.
我们还没谈呢
We still haven't talked, have we?
-没必要谈了  -我觉得要的
- There's no need to. - I think we should.
我是这么想的
Here's how I see it.
你要我过去  我就去了
You asked me to come down. I did.
我们各自对此有自己的想法
We both had ideas about what that could mean.
或许还很相像
Probably very similar ideas.
但随后你又改了主意
But then you changed your mind.
顺其自然吧
So be it.
我们没理由不能保持联络  继续做朋友
There's no reason we can't be in touch or remain friends.
我们不要再自欺欺人了  亚当
Let's not fool ourselves, Adam.
那我不能再打给你了吗
So I won't call again.
-就此结束  -我不是这个意思
- Done. - I'm not saying that.
那你什么意思
What are you saying?
我关心你才给你打电话
I just called because I care about you.
没别的意思
No agenda.
你要想跟我说话  打给我
If you wanna talk again, call me.
不想打  我能理解  都随你
If not, I understand. It's up to you.
你觉得我是无理取闹了
You think I'm being unreasonable?
我觉得你在做你该做的事
I think you're doing whatever it is you need to do,
我不会提出质疑
and I'm not gonna question it.
谢谢你打来问候我
It was sweet of you to call.
你大概得继续工作了
Listen, you probably need to get back to work.
反正我是的  我得挂了
I know I do. I should go.
好的
Yeah. Okay.
-保重  -好的
- Take care. - Okay.
-弗兰克  有空吗  -你们先走吧
- Frank, you got a minute? - I'll see you inside.
我想做州长  并且需要你帮忙
I wanna be governor, and I want your help.
-我还是候选人吗  -是的
- Am I still on the short list? - You are.
我已经一个多月没喝酒了  我戒了
I haven't had a drink in over a month. I'm clean.
是因为我的要求  还是你自己的意愿
Is that because I asked, or because it's what you want?
我也该对自己负责了
It was about time I took responsibility for myself.
对自己负责是一回事  令人敬佩
Taking responsibility is one thing, and it's admirable.
但竞选大州州长  则是另一副局面了
But running for governor of a major state is a whole other ball game.
听我说  弗兰克
Let me tell you something, Frank.
我能成为国会议员
I got elected to congress
就是因为我抓住了机遇
'cause I seized the moment that opportunity struck.
你把我留在了候选人名单上
You kept me on that list.
我想抓住这次机会
I wanna seize that opportunity.
如果你能帮我  我会倾尽全力
If you help me out, I'll give you everything I got.
要的就是这种气概
Well, that's all I've been waiting to hear.
好的  听我说
All right. I'll tell you what.
我还要打些电话  找人落实情况
I need to make some calls, check in with some people.
容我几天时间  我再联络你
Give me a few days. I'll get back to you.
-好的  -还有  彼得...
- Of course. - And, Peter...
我觉得我这才第一次见到真实的你
I feel like I've met the real you for the first time just now.
珍妮特
Janet.
-来得不巧吗  -没事
- Is this a bad time? - No.
没关系的
No, not at all.
抱歉  我都不知道你要来
I'm sorry. I didn't know you were coming.
来  坐我的椅子
Here. Take my chair.
-不用了  没事  -我把这放好
- Oh, no. I'm fine. - I'll take these.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你好  史蒂夫
Hello, Steve.
我去给花添水  马上回来
These could use some water. I'll be right back.
听说你的病情  弗兰西斯和我都很难过
Francis and I were so upset when we heard.
非常抱歉没能早点来探望
I'm sorry I haven't come sooner.
我不想太多人知道
I didn't want too many people knowing.
也是
Yes.
弗兰西斯也想来
Francis wishes he could be here.
他想让你知道他在为你祈福
He wants you to know he's praying for you.
来不了  是吧
Couldn't make it, huh?
是啊  眼下正有场教师大罢工
No, there's a big teachers' strike going on right now,
他已经在办公室里忙了几周了
and he's been stuck in his office for weeks.
我理解  在新闻上看到了
I get it. I saw on the news.
-砸砖事件  -对
- The brick. - Right.
我跟弗兰西斯说
I told Francis that
要是你在就没这种事了
probably wouldn't have happened if you were there.
对  或许吧
No. Probably not.
我从没见过他祈祷
I never seen him pray.
这八年从来没有
Not in eight years.
你刚才说  他在为我祈祷
You said he was praying for me.
你见过我们上教堂啊
You've seen us in church.
确实  但是...
Yeah, but...
我从没进去过
I never went inside.
这些花太美了
They're just gorgeous.
安德伍德太太  非常感谢
Mrs. Underwood, thank you so much.
别见外  叫我克莱尔
Please, call me Claire.
-我知道你还有事情要忙  -当然
- I know you got things to do. - Of course.
有什么需要就联系我  你有我的手机号码
If you need anything at all, call me. You have my cell.
不要客气  抱歉这次贸然而来
Anything at all. And I'm sorry to have surprised you.
哪里  你能过来  真太好了
No. It was so nice of you to come.
谢谢  我知道史蒂夫很高兴
Thank you. I know Steve appreciated it.
看看这个
Check this out.
是泡沫做的
It's foam.
我们有多少这玩意
How many of these we have?
两百  我还能再搞点来
200. But I can get more.
再搞点来
Get more.
来啊
Bring it on!
你得给教师应得的尊重
You need to give the teachers the respect they deserve.
我们没退路了  马蒂
We can't back away from this, Marty.
-我们得面对它  -是他们挑衅我们
- We've gotta face it head-on. - They provoked us.
他们扔的是泡沫  我们是来真的
They were throwing foam. Our guys were throwing punches.
我们会显得像坏人
We're gonna come off the bad guys here.
我知道  我知道
Okay. Okay. I get it. I get it.
但我想把这事办好了
But I wanna be smart about this.
我要采取决定性的措施  结束这一切
I wanna do something definitive that'll put this to bed
-把话题转移回来  -CNN
- and get us back on message. - CNN,
面对面  你和安德伍德
one on one, you and Underwood.
今晚八点
8:00 tonight.
弗兰克是辩论好手
Frank is excellent in debates.
强势点  直接就砖的事跟他对质
Go strong against him. Address the brick right to his face.
-就这样  -安德伍德说  你去他就去
- End of story. - Underwood says he's in if you are.
好  但我需要充分准备  可以吗
Okay. But I want as much prep as possible, okay?
我想模拟一下提问
I want to run questions.
你当中间人  你当安德伍德
You moderate, you play Underwood.
戴这条吧
Wear this one.
然后进屋  我想给你搽点粉
Then come in here. I wanna put powder on you.
演播室那边的人会干的
Well, somebody at the studio can do that.
是  但他们总搽得太多  我来
Yes, and they always cake on too much. I'm doing it.
战争妆容
War paint.
你觉得会有多激烈
How bloody do you think it'll be?
我觉得我很轻易就能了结他
Oh, I think I oughta be able to dispatch with him easily enough.
你记得彼得・罗素吗
Oh, you remember Peter Russo?
他干得不错  一个月滴酒不沾
He's doing well. He hasn't had a drink in a month.
那好啊  我喜欢他
Oh, good for him. I like him.
很好  因为他需要你帮忙
Oh, good, because he could use your help.
-怎么帮  -我们打算让他竞选州长
- How? - We're running him for Governor.
雄心勃勃啊
Ambitious.
我们想在他选区创造工作岗位
We wanna create jobs in his district.
在特拉华河上
It's on the Delaware River.
我想我们或许能弄个法案出来
I thought we might be able to put a bill together.
对经济有促动的
Something with an economic upside.
这件事和造船厂倒闭有关吗
This has to do with the shipyard closing?
我们需要造船厂协会支持他的竞选
We need the shipbuilders' support for his campaign.
你觉得你能起草一个法案
You think you might be able to draft a bill
让他发起吗
that he can sponsor?
我现在的重心在国际项目上  弗兰西斯
I'm really trying to focus on international projects, Francis.
而不是国内立法
Not domestic legislation.
我知道  但我真的需要你的帮助  克莱尔
I understand, but I could really use your help, Claire.
凯瑟琳・杜兰特还欠我们人情吗
Does Catherine Durant still owe us?
你帮谁当上国务卿
When you make someone Secretary of State,
他们这辈子都欠你的
they owe you for life.
我们的滤水器卡在了苏丹海关那里
We're having trouble getting our water filters through Sudanese customs.
-我在车上给她打电话  -明天也不迟
- I'll call from the car. - Tomorrow's fine.
-反正我也会打  -我知道
- I would have done that anyway. - I know.
我准备好上"战场"了
I'm ready for battle.
想来看看吗
You wanna come watch?
-不用了  你去吧  -来吧
- No. You go on ahead. - Oh, come on.
看我给败军致命的一击
Watch me put the final nail in Spinella's coffin.
很好玩的
It'll be fun.
马蒂
Marty.
弗兰克
Frank.
议员先生  你想对此做出回应吗
Congressman, would you like to respond to that?
我会的
Yes, I would.
全国教师罢工
浪费了纳税人二十亿美元
Two billion dollars of taxpayer's money being wasted.
国会真该感到羞愧啊  弗兰克
And congress should be ashamed of itself for that, Frank.
怎么  国会强迫教师罢工了吗  马蒂
Oh, what? Did congress force the teachers to go on strike, Marty?
-不  没有  -是吗  弗兰克
- No, we didn't. - Really, Frank?
你拿教师的集体谈判权相要挟
When you threaten teachers' ability to negotiate as a union,
你威胁他们的工作保障
when you threaten their job security,
你就威胁到了他们的生计
you threaten their livelihood,
当然是你迫使他们起来罢工的
of course you force them to strike.
那我们还迫使他们
And did we also force them
朝人家房子里投砖块吗
to start throwing bricks at people's houses?
我很高兴你提到了这事
You know what? I'm really glad you brought that up,
你明明知道完全没有证据
because you know there's absolutely no proof
证明投砖事件与罢工有任何关系
that that incident had anything to do with this strike.
我想借此机会公开声明
And I wanna take the opportunity to say publicly
我们绝对谴责
that we categorically condemn
任何暴力或恐吓行为
any use of violence whatsoever or intimidation.
你说的不就是
What you're saying essentially
你对你的人领导不力吗
is that you can't control your own people.
我不是这个意思
That is not what I'm saying.
你就是这意思  你的人缺乏组织
That is what you're saying. You're disorganized.
无组织劳工
Disorganized labor.
随你继续重复那个词
You can keep trotting out that phrase all you like,
但你知道我想做什么吗  弗兰克
but you know what I'd like to do, Frank?
我想回到孩子们的教育问题上来
I would like to get back to the issue here of educating our children
回到国会没有尽职的问题上来
and the fact that congress is not living up to their commitment.
你知道我想要什么吗
Well, you know what I would like?
什么
What?
一个道歉
An apology.
即使不向我道歉  那就向我妻子道歉
If not to me, then to my wife.
砖头砸破我家窗户时  非常吓人
When that brick came through our window, it was terrifying.
她现在就站在那儿
She's standing right over there.
-克莱尔  -把镜头对准议员妻子
- Claire? - We need camera two on the wife.
你能直视她的眼睛
Now, why don't you look her in the eye
告诉她你的手下与投砖事件无关吗
and tell her that your people had nothing to do with that brick?
-你是认真的吗  -是的
- Are you serious? - Yes.
好吧
Okay.
安德伍德太太  克莱尔
Mrs. Underwood, Claire,
我真的非常抱歉
I am sincerely sorry
你得经历那样的事
that you had to go through that ordeal, truly.
这事令我生厌
And it actually sickens me
竟然有人让你在自己家感到不安
that someone made you feel unsafe in your own home.
我向你保证  据我所知
And I give you my word that to the best of my knowledge,
我的手下  与此事无关
none of our people had anything to do with it.
你知道我更感到厌恶的是什么吗
But you know what sickens me more?
就是此时此刻  你丈夫居然想利用你
That right now, your husband is using you as a prop
来赢得国家电视台上的辩论
on national television to try and win a debate.
所以我觉得你才该向你妻子道歉  弗兰克
So I think you're the one that owes your wife an apology, Frank.
等你道过歉
And when you're done apologizing,
我们可以回到教育问题上来吗
can we please get back to the issue here of educating our children?
你搞错了  马蒂
No. You've got this wrong, Marty.
教育中没有"你"和"我"
There is no "You" And "I" in education.
"教育"一词里是有
Well, I mean, yes, there's the letters
"U"和"I"这两个字母
"U" and "I" are in the word "Education."
但以E开头的"教育"...
But "Education" with a capital E...
你懂我的意思
You know what I'm talking about.
我不知道
I don't think I do.
不  你知道的  马蒂
Yes, you do, Marty.
U和I  教育
U and I-- Education.
怎么  接下来的辩论
So, what, we're gonna waste the
要浪费在念"教育"的元音字母上吗
rest of this debate naming all the vowels in--
我很愿意玩元音字母游戏
I'm happy to play the vowel game.
你想玩玩吗
You wanna play the vowel game with me?
好的  你觉得我欠
All right. U think I O
你一个道歉
U A apology.
但你搞错了
But no, no, no.
你欠我...
U o I...
有意思  你漏掉了"教育"里的E
Interesting. You left out E for "Education."
-所以还是...  -澄清
- So let-- - Defecation--
启迪  抱歉  哈哈
Edification. I'm sorry. LOL.
你这么喜欢《芝麻街》[美国知名儿童节目]
You like sesame street so much?
怎么不把孩子们应得的钱还给他们
Why don't you give the kids the money they deserve?
我想说的是...教育...
What I'm trying to say about education...
嗯
Well,
看来学校没停课
I guess school's still in session.
你倒给我上了一课  马蒂
I guess you schooled me there, Marty.
请继续吧
Let's move on. Please.
撇开笑谈  还有许多重要议题
Humor aside, there are more important issues out there.
我从未想要把你牵扯进来
I had no intention of bringing you into this.
那不在计划之内  否则我会提前说的
It wasn't part of a plan. I would've told you if it was.
我知道
I know.
我突然就想到了  顺势说了出来
The idea just struck me, and I went with it.
我并不介意你临场自由发挥
I don't mind that you improvised.
我只是希望你能做好点
I just wish you'd done it better.
在昨晚本台的一场辩论当中
Congressman Frank Underwood says
弗兰西斯・安德伍德议员说
he got, quote, "Schooled" by AFT spokesman
美国教师联合会发言人兼首席顾问
and chief strategist, Martin Spinella,
马丁・斯比奈拉给他"上了一课"
during a debate last night on this network.
过去24小时里
In the past 24 hours,
电视新闻节目和网络
reruns of the gaffe have played non-stop
不停地重播议员的失态
on TV news programs and the Internet.
合成电子乐的YouTube视频
A YouTube clip set to techno music
已有超过30万的点击量
has logged more than 300,000 hits
并衍生出了不少恶搞
and spawned dozens of other spoofs.
和我玩元音
不
No
E  O  I
E O I
大写"E"
with a capital "E"
教育  哈哈
education LOL
这个拙劣程度
That was as clumsy
李・哈维・奥斯瓦尔德  被指刺杀肯尼迪  在转狱时被人当众击毙
和李・哈维・奥斯瓦尔德的转狱不相上下
as the Lee Harvey Oswald prison transfer.
他怎么想的
What was he thinking?
等我一下
Just give me one second.
在街尾有家熟食店
There's a deli. Down the street.
帕特  多谢你能来
Patti, thanks for coming.
请坐  要喝咖啡吗
Sit down. You want some coffee?
谢了  不用
No, thanks. I'm good.
比尔・马赫  HBO一档时政脱口秀的主持人
你昨晚看《马赫脱口秀》了吗
Hey, did you see Bill Maher last night?
没看
No, I didn't.
是有关CNN的辩论
Oh, it was about the CNN thing.
弗兰克  我得承认  是挺逗的
I have to admit, Frank, it was kinda funny.
那我要去看重播了
Well, I'll have to catch a rerun.
你怎么样  罢工的事还好吗
How you doing? You holding up all right with the strike?
我们谈谈宾夕法尼亚吧
Let's talk about Pennsylvania.
我有候选人了
I have your candidate.
彼得・罗素  第一国会选区
Peter Russo. First Congressional District.
我们划掉他了
We crossed him off.
我知道  那是个错误
I know. It's a mistake.
他年轻帅气  聪明有为
He's young, he's handsome. He's bright.
出了宾州  没人知道他是谁
Nobody knows who he is outside of Philadelphia.
既没有金主捐款  又没有竞选组织机构
There's no donor base, no infrastructure.
你让民主党全国委员会给我启动资金
You start me off with funding from the DNC
我就能为他召集一支军队
and I'll raise an army around this guy.
我会亲自监督他的竞选
I will personally oversee his campaign.
这是最佳人选了吗
Is that the best we can do?
有什么比好画师手里的白纸更好
What's better than a blank slate in the right hands?
艾德  你快走
Ed, you need to go.
议员  您有空吗
Congressman, do you have a moment?
谢谢你  帕特
Thank you, Patti.
-叫他给我打电话  -我会的
- Have him call me. - I will.
艾德  走吧
Ed? Please.
-怎么回事  -我来处理
- What is going on? - I'm taking care of it.
就一会儿  先生  求您了
One second, sir. Please.
好吧  长话短说  密查姆
All right. Make it fast, Meechum.
要我开这个口很不容易
It's not easy for me to ask this,
但我想您能否跟我们头儿说点好话
but I was wondering if you could put in a good word with my boss.
说好话
A good word?
他们准备解雇我  先生
They're going to discharge me, sir.
我很清楚是自己搞砸了
I messed up. I'm fully aware.
但这份工作对我意义重大
But my job, it means everything to me,
我知道您的好话会...
and I know a good word from you would...
就个人而言  我对你没意见  密查姆
Look, I have nothing against you personally, Meechum,
但我不能掺和到这些事里去
but I can't get involved in these sort of affairs.
规矩就是规矩
There's protocols and rules.
先生  求您了  如果您和卡迪夫谈
Sir, please, if you spoke to Cardiff--
我无能为力
There is nothing that I can do.
如果有谁能说服队长
If anyone can convince the captain,
那一定就是您了  议员
it would be you, Congressman.
抱歉  祝你好运  密查姆
I'm sorry. I wish you all the best, Meechum.
道格
Doug.
巴尼・豪尔怎么说
What did Barney Hull say?
我们会在第一时间知道
That we'd be the first to know.
真不敢相信到现在都没报警电话
I can't believe there hasn't been a single 911 call.
有很多
There's been plenty.
只是没有我们要的那种
It's just not the sort we're after.
倒是有亚特兰大那个孩子
We got that kid in Atlanta.
不  必须得在这里  我不能坐飞机
No, it's got to be here. I can't be getting on a plane.
那样就太投机了
It looks too opportunistic.
或许我们该扩大点范围
Maybe if we open it up a little bit.
不  我们不能降低标准
No, we cannot lower our standards.
再耐心等等
We just have to be patient.
元音曲
新规则  既然辩论结束了
New rule-- now that the debate's over,
弗兰克・安德伍德该告诉我们到底怎么回事
Frank Underwood has to tell us what the hell that was.
说真的  议员  你是在搞笑吗
Seriously, Congressman, was that a joke?
我很久没听过这样的东西了
I haven't seen something just lay there like that
自从...
since, uh...
我得追溯到我的毕业舞会了
I gotta go all the way back to my prom night.
我们能解决这次罢工吗
Can we just settle this strike please?
教师离开教室太久了
Teachers have been out of the classroom for so long,
初中生都开始"嘿咻"了
middle schoolers are starting to have sex with each other.
别看了
Enough.
真不知道你为什么要看它
I don't know why you had it on in the first place.
我爱你  弗兰西斯
I love you, Francis.
我知道
I know.
我们该经常对彼此说这话
We should say that more often to each other.
我得去理下思路
I need to clear my head.
机场北面和东面
...north and east of the airport.
会议之前及时帮我准备好
I'm gonna need that in time for that meeting.
彼得  我们聊聊吧
Peter, let's talk.
我找过帕特里夏・惠特克了
So. I've spoken to Patricia Whittaker.
她同意了
She's on board.
民主党国家委员会
You'll be getting four
将为你提供四百万美元启动资金
million in start-up funding from the DNC.
我来挑选团队  你在八月宣布
I'll pick the team. You announce in August.
但竞选今天就开始了
But the campaign starts today.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
我已经草拟了一份竞选纲领
I've already put together a platform.
大部分还很宽泛  但我们可以再打磨
It's mostly broad strokes, but we can hone it.
很好  我们的首要任务
Good. The first thing we need to address
是你戒酒的事
is your sobriety.
这点你不用担心
Oh, you don't need to worry about that.
你参加聚会了吗
Have you been going to meetings?
你指嗜酒者互诫会
You mean AA?
-对  -我对那个没兴趣
- Yes. - That's not really my thing.
如果你要我帮你
If you want my help,
参加互诫会是我的唯一要求
then going to meetings is my one requirement.
我知道我酗酒  弗兰克
I know I had a problem, Frank.
我承认
I accept that.
我会对此负责
And I've taken responsibility for that,
但我认为我不需要参加互诫会
but I don't think going to meetings is necessary.
你恢复期不能这么紧张  彼得
You cannot white-knuckle your recovery, Peter.
这次竞选将是你这辈子
This campaign will be the hardest thing
做的最艰难的事
you've ever done in your life.
我知道  我有心理准备
I realize that. I'm prepared for that.
你以为自己准备好了
You think you are.
但我们要杜绝风险
But we can't take any chances.
党内对你寄予厚望
The party's investing in you.
我得确保你也全力以赴
I need to make sure you're investing in yourself.
好  我会做任何必要的事
All right. I'll do whatever I have to do.
很好  从明天早上开始
Good. You'll start tomorrow morning.
-道格会带你去  -斯坦普
- Doug will take you. - Stamper?
他戒酒14年了
He's been sober 14 years.
道格也酗酒吗
Doug has a drinking problem?
曾经  已经戒了  他会做你的保证人
Had. Not anymore. He'll be your sponsor.
与此同时  我要你去见我妻子  克莱尔
In the meantime, I want you to meet with my wife, Claire.
她运作净水计划
She runs the Clean Water Initiative.
她在等你
She's expecting you,
取消你的行程  现在就过去
so clear your schedule and head over there now.
弗兰克
Frank.
谢谢你
Thank you.
愿意相信我
For believing in me.
你会成为优秀的候选人  彼得
You're gonna make a great candidate, Peter.
关闭造船厂空出了一千英亩国有土地
The shipyard closing frees up 1,100 acres of federal land.
我们的目标是通过特拉华河流域的法案
Our goal is to pass a watershed act for the Delaware River.
我们以不破坏环境的方式开发土地
We develop the land in an environmentally-responsible way,
同时创造就业岗位
creating jobs in the process.
-多少岗位  -上千个
- How many jobs? - Thousands.
目标收益两亿美元
We're aiming for the $200-million mark.
我们有很多事要做
We got a lot of work to do.
没错  但你可以从
We do, but you can start
选区在流域内的议员入手
with the congressman whose districts fall within the watershed.
你能不能让我看下草案
Do you have a draft of the bill you can show me?
我们从没发起过环境法规
We haven't sponsored any environmental legislation.
我是史蒂夫  不要打电话  来看看我
草案等和你的同事商议后再定
We'll draft it in consultation with your staff.
吉莉安是我们这边的主负责人
Gillian will be the point person on our end.
我没有任何立法经验
I don't have any legislation experience.
-我会帮你  -什么时候开始
- I'll help you. - When do we start?
已经开始了
We just did.
麻烦向他介绍下调研团队
Will you introduce him to the research team?
-我一会儿就过去  -好
- I'll be there in one second. - Sure.
明天行吗
总统先生
Mr. President?
结束这一切
I want it over.
越快越好
As soon as possible.
修改法案  弗兰克
Gut the bill, Frank.
不惜一切代价结束罢工
Do whatever's necessary to end this.
总统先生  如果我们现在妥协
Mr. President, if we give in now,
公众不会认为你成功了
the public won't credit you with a victory.
连伪胜利都不算
Not even a hollow one.
他们会把这视做一次惨败
They'll chalk it up as a colossal defeat.
那是你的责任  弗兰克
Well, that's on you, Frank.
是你让事态一发不可收拾
You let this situation devolve to where it is.
我已经因为美国史上
I've already been blamed
规模最大的教师罢工而备受指摘
for the largest teacher's strike in US history.
我不能对它无休止的拖延而负责
I won't be held accountable for it dragging on months and months.
总统先生  只有您能终止罢工
Mr. President, we have to end this strike on your terms.
其他人都不行
Not anyone else's.
怎么做  在CNN和马蒂・斯比奈拉辩论吗
How? By debating Marty Spinella on CNN?
先生  您一直都很信任我
Sir, you have placed your faith in me thus far.
我恳求您一如既往
I would ask that you continue to do so.
不论你在做什么  弗兰克  都不奏效
Whatever you're doing, Frank, isn't working,
所以我要介入了
so I'm stepping in.
按琳达说的  修改法案
Gut the bill. Like Linda said.
不
No.
我很抱歉  总统先生  我做不到
I'm sorry, Mr. President, but I will not do that.
你是不是被骄傲冲昏了头脑  弗兰克
Are you letting pride cloud your judgment, Frank?
恕我直言  先生
Respectfully, sir,
恐怕是您被恐惧冲昏了头脑
you're allowing fear to cloud yours.
对自由世界最有权势的人说不
Not an easy thing to say no to the most powerful man
可不容易
in the free world.
但有些时候  要想赢得上司的尊重
But sometimes the only way to gain your superior's respect
就只能违抗他
is to defy him.
日程表上还有什么安排  琳达
What do we have on the schedule, Linda?
您要会见...
Your meeting with the...
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
-提纲在你那儿吗  -在这儿
- Do you have my briefing? - Right here.
好  我们来浏览一下
Good. Let's look it over.
和彼得谈得怎么样
Hi. How'd it go with Peter?
还不错
It went well.
他投入吗
Is he game?
很投入
Completely.
太好了  谢谢
Ugh. Thank you.
可让我松了一口气
That's a big weight off my shoulders.
你听起来累坏了
You sound tired.
又累又烦躁
Tired. Impatient.
我能帮上什么忙吗
What can I do?
不用了  这事只能听天由命
Nothing. This one's up to fate.
我不喜欢听天由命
I don't like when we leave things to fate.
我也是
Neither do I.
那我今晚要独守空房了吗
Does that mean I'm gonna have the bed to myself tonight?
或许吧
Probably.
不能让道格独当一面吗
Can't Doug man the fort?
可以  但我肯定会辗转反侧
Well, he could, but I'd just toss and turn.
既然睡不着  还不如留在这儿工作
If I'm not gonna sleep, I might as well not sleep here.
我会开着手机
Well, I'll leave the ringer on.
想要人陪伴就打给我
Call me if you want company.
好的  晚安
I will. Good night.
晚安
Good night.
你回家吧  剩下的交给我就行了
You should go home. I can take it from here.
保持警醒  对灵魂有好处
Vigilance. It's good for the soul.
10-59  十六街与Q街拐角  10-59
10-59. Corner of 16th and Q. 10-59.
什么事
What's that?
妨碍治安
Disorderly conduct.
你相信有因果报应吗
Do you believe in karma?
绝对不信
Absolutely not.
但我信
Well, I do.
起码今晚我信
At least tonight.
给卡迪夫队长打个电话
Get Captain Cardiff on the phone.
处理一下密查姆的事
Let's do something about Meechum.
怎么处理
What?
帮他保住饭碗
Get him his job back.
可他开枪了
He fired his weapon.
只是反应过度罢了
He overreacted.
立刻打给卡迪夫
Cardiff. On the phone. Now.
南茜  请帮我接卡迪夫队长
Nancy, give me Captain Cardiff, please.
反正也是干等  不如做点有用的事
We might as well do one productive thing while we wait.
这对我来说只是举手之劳
It requires very little of me
但对他却意义重大
and will mean the world to him.
是笔很划算的投资
It's a very inexpensive investment.
你好  先生  我是道格・斯坦普
Hello, sir. This is Doug Stamper.
弗兰西斯・安德伍德想和您谈谈
I have Francis Underwood for you.
他在线上
I got him on.
队长  我知道很晚了
Captain, I know it's late,
但我想跟你谈谈艾德华・密查姆的事
but I'd like to talk to you about Edward Meechum.
早上好  先生们
Good morning, gentlemen.
谢谢
Thank you.
饿了吗
Are you hungry?
进来的时候麻烦吗
You have any trouble getting in?
没  他们只是让我把吃的过了两遍安检
Nah, they made me put it through the X-ray machine twice.
希望没被烤焦
So I hope it didn't overcook it.
弗兰克  你总是多给  实在太多了
Frank, you always pay too much. This is way too much.
算是谢谢你送来
For the inconvenience.
你光顾我的小店都有二十年了
You know, 20 years you been coming to my joint.
这是我第一次到你工作的地方
This the first time I been to yours.
觉得怎么样
What do you think?
挺不错的
I could get used to it.
随时欢迎
Well, you're welcome any time.
多谢  弗莱迪
Thank you, Freddy.
别客气  弗兰克
Always, Frank.
第三街446...发生一起...
Got a... 446 3rd Street...
是一起驾车枪击
That's a drive-by shooting.
查查详情
Get details.
先生  多谢您帮我向队长说情
Sir, I want to thank you for talking to the Captain.
他说您给他打了电话
He told me you called,
我对您感激不尽
and I can't tell you how grateful I am.
我希望你仔细听我要说的话
I want you to listen very closely to what I'm about to say.
从这一刻起  你就是一块石头
From this moment on, you are a rock.
万物不侵  丝毫不吐
You absorb nothing, you say nothing,
坚不可摧
and nothing breaks you.
-明白了吗  -是的  先生
- Is that clear? - Yes, sir.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
史蒂夫
Steve?
我先出去了
I'll leave you be.
珍妮特去哪了
Where, uh-- where's Janet?
过去几周她一直都守在这里
She's been here every day for the last few weeks.
我让她回家休息
I told her go home, get some rest.
一切还好吗
Well, is everything okay?
你发短信说很重要
Your text said it was important.
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know how to put this.
就是  我
The thing is, I...
我想了
I've been thinking...
很多
a lot.
想我这辈子
About my life.
想我还未完成的事
About the things I haven't done.
还没来得及说的话
Things I haven't said.
我恨你丈夫
I hate your husband.
很多人都恨他
A lot of people do.
过去八年  我一直守着他
The past eight years, I watched over him.
但我看的并不是他
But it wasn't him I was watching.
每次我看到你
And every time I saw you,
听到你的声音
every time I heard your voice,
我想的都是
all I could think to myself was,
天哪  我真愿付出一切跟你在一起
"Jesus, what I wouldn't give."
这种想法在我脑海中不知盘旋了多少次
I can't tell you how many times I thought about that.
你知道弗兰西斯向我求婚时说了什么吗
You know what Francis said to me when he proposed?
他说的每个字我都记得
I remember his exact words.
他说  克莱尔  如果你只想要幸福
He said, "Claire, if all you want is happiness,
那就拒绝吧
Say no.
我不会跟你生一堆孩子
I'm not gonna give you a couple of kids
然后数着日子等退休
and count the days until retirement.
我保证你免受这些痛苦
I promise you freedom from that.
也永远不会无聊
I promise you'll never be bored."
他是唯一一个...
You know, he was the only man--
有很多人向我求婚
and there were a lot of others who proposed.
但他是唯一一个懂我的
But he was the only one who understood me.
他没把我看作什么女神
He didn't put me on some pedestal.
他知道我不想受崇拜或者溺爱
He knew that I didn't want to be adored or coddled.
于是他拉起了我的手  为我戴上了戒指
So he took my hand and he put a ring on it.
因为他知道我会答应的
Because he knew I'd say yes.
他懂得如何获得他想要的东西
He's a man who knows how to take what he wants.
这是你想要的吗
Is this what you wanted?
你想要这样吗
Is that the way you wanted it?
停下  停下
Stop. Stop.
求你了  求你了  快停下
Please. Please. Stop.
别这样
Don't.
你跟我说了实话
You told me your truth.
现在你也了解我了
Now you know mine.
彼得・罗素
我是彼得
Hey, it's Peter.
我不指望你会打回来
I don't expect you to call me back,
但我想告诉你我昨晚决定戒酒了
but I wanted to let you know I stopped drinking last night,
今早还第一次去了嗜酒者互诫会
and I went to my first AA meeting this morning.
我要去找那些我曾伤害过的人做些弥补
Um, I'm supposed to reach out and make amends to those I've hurt.
但我打电话的真正原因
But I guess the real reason I called you
是想告诉你我爱你  也很想你
is just to say I love you and I miss you.
希望你一切都好
I hope you're well.
这是工作  不是娱乐
This is work, not play.
那你为什么亲自过来
Then why'd you bother coming over?
我本希望你赤身裸体地来开门
I was hoping you'd answer the door naked.
那是娱乐
That would be play.
那是劳逸结合
That would be work with a view.
抱歉让你失望了
Sorry to disappoint.
一条推特能写几个字
How many characters in a tweet?
140字
140.
按我说的写  告诉我字数
Type this, let me know where you land.
八岁华盛顿男孩
"Eight-year-old Washington DC boy
被黑帮火拼的流弹击中身亡
killed by a stray bullet in gangland shoot-out."
还剩61个字
61 characters left.
本该在学校里
"Should have been in school"?
还剩30
30 left.
斯比奈拉难辞其咎  问号
"Spinella to blame?"
128个字
128.
发送吧
Press "Send."
告诉我名字和细节
Now give me a name, details.
泰勒・戴维斯  弗农・贝克小学三年级学生
Tyler Davis. Third grader at Vernon Baker Elementary.
今天不到中午时在东南部自己家外面被打死
Shot outside his home in southeast just before noon today.
发送了  你去哪
Sent. Where are you going?
-去见孩子的母亲  -你不想...
- To see the mother. - You don't wanna...?
还有工作要做  我晚点会来
There's work to do. I'll see you later tonight.
泰勒从不干坏事
Tyler never did anything wrong.
是个好孩子
He was a good boy.
大家都喜欢他
Everybody loved him.
会没事的
It's okay.
如果泰勒的学校在上课
If Tyler's school had been in session,
他就不会被错杀了
this senseless killing would have never taken place.
我们得即刻结束这场罢工
We need to end this strike now
让孩子们回到学校  那是他们该去的地方
and get all our children back in school where they belong
以免此类悲剧再次发生
before we risk another death like this.
斯比奈拉先生  我这就去国会大厦
So, Mr. Spinella, I am headed to the capitol right now,
我会待在那里  直到你愿意跟我会面磋商
and I will remain there until you are ready to meet and talk
结束这场毫无意义的罢工
so that we can end this pointless strike.
谢谢你们的到来
Thank you all for coming.
我们进去吧
Let's go back inside.
斯比奈拉先生  就一个问题
Mr. Spinella, one question...
斯比奈拉先生目前无可奉告
Mr. Spinella is not to make a comment at this time.
无可奉告  无可奉告
No comment. No comment.
谢谢
Thank you.
弗兰克
Frank.
说吧
So?
你说你想谈谈
You said you wanted to talk.
你说你想达成一个妥协
You said you wanted to work out a compromise.
我撒谎了
I lied.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我完全没有跟你达成妥协的意思
I have no intention of working out a compromise.
那为什么让我来  弗兰克
So then why the fuck are we here, Frank?
你有什么毛病
What the hell's the matter with you?
你以为这是游戏吗
You think this is some kind of a game?
不
No.
这些人都是有家要养的
These are real people with families to feed.
能别敲了吗
Would you please stop that?
别敲什么
Stop what?
再数五秒钟  我就走
In five seconds, I'm out of here.
一  二  三
One. Two. Three.
-四  -再见  弗兰克
- Four. - Goodbye, Frank.
你知道你我之间的不同吗  马蒂
You know the difference between you and me, Marty?
什么
What?
我是一个出生在
I'm a white-trash cracker from a
鸟不拉屎的白人镇上的无名之徒
white-trash town that no one would even bother to piss on.
差别在于
But here's the difference--
我自己努力取得了成就
I've made something of myself.
我进入了国会  人们尊重我
I have the keys to the capitol. People respect me.
而你  仍然狗屁不是
But you, you're still nothing.
你就是个自负的意大利佬
You're just an uppity dago
穿件好衣服  为工会卖命
in an expensive suit turning tricks for the unions.
没人尊重工会了  马蒂
Nobody respects the unions anymore, Marty.
他们行将就木  也没有人尊重你
They're dying. And no one respects you.
你这辈子至多就是
The most you'll ever make of yourself
给我这样的人吹箫
is blowing men like me.
真正有权势的人
Men with real power.
是的  我在这儿就闻得到你嘴里的骚气
Yes. I can smell the cock on your breath from here.
你以为你能激怒我
You think you can get under my skin?
我知道我能
I know I can.
给我滚吧  弗兰克
Kiss my ass, Frank.
你不敢走出去
You can't afford to walk out.
看我敢不敢
Watch me.
我手上有一个死去的贫困儿童
I've got a dead, underprivileged kid in my pocket.
你有什么
What do you have?
我有两百万尊敬的教师
I have 2 million honorable teachers.
说得好  但我还有更好的
Fair enough. But I got something even better.
来吧  打开它
Go ahead. Open it.
好
Okay.
我陪你玩
I'll play your game.
你是个白痴
You're an idiot.
斯坦普扔的
Stamper threw it.
你真是满嘴胡话
You're full of shit.
不  就是他扔的
Oh, no, Stamper threw the brick.
而且我让克莱尔把保安支开了
And I made sure Claire distracted my security.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
想想你还让我向我妻子道歉
And to think you wanted me to apologize to my wife.
你真这么不择手段  弗兰克
You would do something that low, Frank?
我安排了砖块袭窗  马蒂
I arranged the brick, Marty,
就像我安排了这场会面
just like I arranged this meeting this afternoon.
退后  弗兰克
Back off, Frank.
你为什么不跪下来  那才是你该做的
Why don't you just get down on your knees where you really belong?
退后  弗兰克
Back off, Frank.
因为你唯一能从我这儿得到的东西
Because the only thing you're gonna get from me
-就是喷在...  -去你妈的
- is come on your-- - Fuck you!
里面没事吧
Everything okay in there?
听着  我会告诉他们是你挑衅我
Look, I'll-- I'll tell them you provoked me.
我会告诉他们是你亲自扔的砖块
I'll tell them that you threw the brick yourself.
谁会相信你呢
And who's going to believe you?
你刚刚袭击了美国国会议员
You just assaulted a United States congressman,
这可是重罪
which is a felony.
但我不会起诉你  马蒂
But I'm not gonna press charges, Marty.
因为罢工要即刻停止
Because the strike ends now.
你觉得会留疤吗
You think it'll leave a scar?
我脸皮厚
I have a thick skin.
下次你让我请人进门喝咖啡的时候
The next time you ask me to invite someone in for coffee,
务必确保没人会开枪  好吗
will you please make sure no guns go off?
我会尽我所能
I'll do my best.
我今天又去见了史蒂夫
I saw Steve again today.
他怎么样
How is he?
很痛苦
In a lot of pain.
我要去看望一下吗
Should I go see him?
不用
I don't think you need to.
佐伊・巴恩斯
Zoe Barnes.
等他死了  我们该出钱为他办葬礼
When he dies, we'll pay for his funeral.
你不需要接吗
You don't need to take it?
不  我今天的工作已经结束了
No. I'm done with work today.
翻译  ~某人
翻译   waterlike
翻译  某豚
翻译  和小蟹
翻译  天意
翻译   sakura
翻译  小饭
翻译  u油
时间轴  暮暮.Lee
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第六集
人人影视倾情奉献